redfcu.org 2019-01-01

# FACTS

                                                                                                         rev. June 2015
                  WHAT DOES REDSTONE FEDERAL CREDIT UNION® DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL
FACTS             INFORMATION?
                  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the
Why?              right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and
                  protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with
What?             us. This information can include:
                       •    Social Security number and income
                       •    Payment history and credit card and other debt
                       •    Credit history and checking account information
                  When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
                  All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In
How?              the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal
                  information; the reasons Redstone Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this
                  sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal              Does Redstone Federal Credit Union share?         Can you limit this sharing?
information
For our everyday business purposes –                                 Yes                                      No
such as to process your transactions,
maintain your account(s), respond to
court orders and legal investigations, or
report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –                                         Yes                                      No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial                             Yes                                      No
companies
For our affiliates’ everyday business                                Yes                                      No
purposes –
information about your transactions and
experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business                                No                                 We don’t share
purposes –
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                  No                                 We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                   No                                 We don’t share
                       Call toll-free 1-800-234-1234 or go to www.redfcu.org
Questions?

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?          Redstone Federal Credit Union
What we do
How does Redstone Federal Credit Union To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
protect my personal information?       and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                       These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                       and buildings.
How does Redstone Federal Credit Union We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?
                                            •   apply for a loan or open an account
                                            •   pay your bills or use your debit or credit card
                                            •   make deposits and withdrawals from your account
                                       We also collect your personal information from others such as
                                       credit bureaus, affiliates or other companies
Why can’t I limit all sharing?         Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                            •   sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                information about your creditworthiness
                                            •   affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                            •   sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                       State laws and individual companies may give you additional
                                       rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                             Companies related by common ownership or control. They can
                                       be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                            •   Our affiliates include companies with Redstone in their
                                                name; financial companies such as Redstone Services
                                                Group, LLC, Redstone Services Group, LLC DBA Redstone
                                                Insurance Services; and Redstone Title Services, LLC and
                                                nonfinancial companies such as Redstone Consulting
                                                Group, LLC.
Nonaffiliates                          Companies not related by common ownership or control. They
                                       can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                            •   Redstone Federal Credit Union does not share with
                                                nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                        A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies
                                       that together market financial products or services to you.
                                            •   Our joint marketing partners include insurance providers
                                                and online financial service providers.
